robotceleb.com 2013-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Robot Celeb

**RobotCeleb.com Privacy Statement:**

Thank you for visiting RobotCeleb.com, a DS Internet, LLC. site. DS Internet, LLC has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the RobotCeleb.com website.

The Information We Collect

At some DS Internet, LLC sites, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums, or become a member of the network. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At some other DS Internet, LLC sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a giftonline and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient’s name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site’s activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), internet protocol address and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our membership agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your request to view a particular page or site.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

If you choose to submit content for publication, we may publish your screen name, email address, internet protocol address and other information you have provided to us.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

Certain DS Internet, LLC sites does not disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to you.

Finally, the DS Internet, LLC sites covered by this Privacy Policy will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

The DS Internet, LLC sites covered by this Privacy Notice sometimes may offer content that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. DS Internet, LLC has no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The DS Internet, LLC site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

Some of the DS Internet, LLC sites covered by this Privacy Notice may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you.

Cookies

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

Registration Forms  
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their first and last name, and email address). We ask for credit card information over a secure server only.

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. RobotCeleb.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Data Quality/Access  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

1\. You can send email to webmaster@RobotCeleb.com  
2\. Users can, at any time, check and/or edit their user profile in our database.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  
webmaster@RobotCeleb.com
